Hoang Gia Hung

Frontend Developer

giahung197bg@gmail.com

0

in





About

Hi, my name is Hung, i'm 26 years old. I got a bachelor of Electronics Telecommunication Engineering at Ha Noi University of Science and Technology (2015 - 2020). Besides, i am really passionate about Javascript and Web Development.

I am also an open-source enthusiast and maintainer. I love how collaboration and knowledge sharing happens through open-source and I am happy to see what I do could eventually feedback to the community and industry.

Projects

Hillridge 7

Agricultural construction insurance

Maby [↗]

Build system appointments and booking management

Maby Salon ^对

Build system appointments and booking management

Gourmetmarket Thailand 7

Build e-commerce website

Summoners Arena 7

Build a marketplace

XO Sections ↗

Build UI section for the app on Shopify

More Projects...

Work Experience

AgileTech Vietnam Frontend Developer

Dec 2020 - Present | Nhân Hòa, quận Thanh Xuân, Hà Nội

- Worked on developing and maintaining the projects of the company.
- Training new members of the company.

Beau Agency Vietnam Frontend Developer Intern

Dec 2019 - Dec 2020 | Hoàng Văn Thái, Thanh Xuân, Hà Nội

Worked on developing and maintaining the company's e-commerce, landing page website

• Developed and maintained the project on shopify platform.

Stacks

Frontend TypeScript, JavaScript, Reactjs, Nextjs, Vite

Backend Node, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Nginx, Docker

DevOps Firebase

Languages C/C++

Education

Electronics Telecommunication Engineering, Engineer, Hanoi university of science and technology Sep 2015 - Sep 2020

Languages

Vietnamese (Native speaker), English (Beginner)

Online Version

Last updated at August 13th 2023, 5:58:19 pm